“O&Partners”
Star
Huh?
- Star?
- Star!
uh? Star! Here, here!
Star!
Hey, Attorney Kang!
- Oh, star!
-Are you okay?
- No, why did you fall!
- Fish oil!
I think your lower body is a bit weak.
Oh, you have to be careful, really.
It hurts!
Hey, sister!
About a person's physical weaknesses
I'm not mentioning it!
Oh, it's okay
The lower body may be a bit weak.
No, with someone else's lower body
You guys, what?
Beat the drum and play the janggu
That's not true!
Hey, man!
To you, man!
What are you doing now?
To our client!
Oh, you're a client?
What kind of client is this mutt…
What a mutt!
That animal derogatory comment
Cancel now
Ha…
Oh Jeongin!
Star~
- Wow, the stars were surprised, right?
- Ugh~
- Oh my, our star
- You were surprised.
Hey, this isn't it!
Don't even ask my doctor
How could you send someone to a place like that!
What kind of place is that?
Can you speak so I can understand?
If you are an executive, act like an executive.
Give me a position that suits my career!
Only chaebols and members of the National Assembly
How many people have passed through my hands…
Asking a doctor
When the other party has a choice
Isn’t that right, Attorney David Kang?
what?
If I've said everything I want to say
Can I go?
Oh, I have a meeting.
It's management.
But is it raining outside?
Is it clear?
Phew…
I'm sorry
What I have now
All I have is these sweatpants.
Wow, your stomach is wet too, here.
Oh my, really...
- No no…
- But for me, yes?
I will do it
Ah, yes
Then I will quickly go and do this
I'll dry it right away, yes.
Hey, your pants are nice, really.
Let's understand the situation first.
There must be a reason
In Korea
The most expensive law firm, O&Partners.
not worth a penny
Why we created a team dedicated to public interest
Star
Oh my, you’re so kind.
and
Why did you send me here
So this mutt…
So this
accused of stealing from a client
Are you being sued?
Stealing Byeol-i?
This is nonsense.
We adopted Byul.
This is my child
Soyeon here
I'm an abandoned dog protection activist.
Wandering around without a necklace
After discovering and protecting Byul...
I couldn't find the landlord
He was working part-time
To the dog cafe owner
I asked you to adopt me, yes.
But later
The previous owner showed up?
It's a year and a half
How come I didn't look for it for a year and a half?
It's finally appeared...
I really...
It's a whim
If a child is sick
Throw it away and later
If the new owner takes good care of it and it gets better,
Because it's mine
People who tell me to give it up are like this
There are often
If it's like this
Rescue and adopt abandoned dogs
All legal procedures will fall apart.
Lawyer Kang
yes, that's right
It's a really important event.
We must solve this
surely
yes, yes
Well, it's really important...
It's an incident
During the trial of the chairman of a conglomerate
Theft of a mutt…
- under…
- Our star
I can never let you go
never
now never again
‘Never again’?
that…
When I discovered it
How was the dog's condition?
Uh, what about stars?
The tail is so limp...
It felt like I had starved for a very long time.
I approached him and he didn't bark.
I pay a lot of attention
It looked very difficult
Where did you find it?
It was Seongbukcheon
At the time of discovery
You mean there was no dog collar?
There was no built-in chip?
yes
Because you are an abandoned dog protection activist.
Of course, you followed all the procedures, right?
Yes, of course
What is a procedure?
Ah, this field
I don't know.
When an abandoned dog is found
According to Article 39 of the Animal Protection Act...
Oh, it's written there?
Watch and listen
Local government or
If you report it to the animal protection center,
to find the owner
Announcements are made for more than a week
Even after ten days
If the owner doesn't show up
Finding a new owner...
Oh, I want to tie that guy's hands.
He can't talk if he doesn't move his hands?
New owner legally acquires ownership
Hey~
You are an expert. What field is this?
Ah, legally, whatever.
I think I have a new owner.
What's the problem?
Now the former owner
You're being reckless, whatever.
Do you need to be scared?
That's right, yeah
But that recklessness
Ha, this is usually reckless
Because it's not
Oh, what!
- Uh...
- Oh my!
oops, sorry
our star
Ha, he was big.
I'm very scared
I'm a kid who never bites people.
don't be scared
Byeol-iga
I like Attorney Kang.
The puppies
I recognize good people quickly.
Uh, uh, sure.
I don’t really like dogs… Ugh!
- Why, why, why, why!
- oh!
- Star!
- Oh, star!
tail wagging
Watch me follow you
No, why do you keep following me?
- Uh, uh...
- Star!
Ah, look what I like
First of all
Need to find the weak link
To dig up information
To a law firm
Mushrooms?
Is he a carpenter?
Hehehe
- Well, go ahead.
- Oh, yeah.
Are you a fan of Toraie?
How on earth did Byeonsi pass?
"Patient Person"
Hey, look at his eyes
You look very angry on your face
bingo
Let's have a cup of coffee
Yes?
coffee
good
Wow
No, as the youngest
You served as a judge dedicated to corruption?
Even though you graduated from high school?
Ha, really
sorry
kid, what
Hey, what are you sorry about?
Education, qualifications
It doesn't matter much
The only thing that matters is
effort
Right?
Effort will never betray you
Me at first glance
Why should I say this?
yellowing
I see it
I am not the type of person who will be satisfied here.
Huh!
Well, do you see that?
Sure
Oh, Dr. Oh Kyu-jang
Make me the team leader here
Why did you send it?
Have you discovered hidden talent?
Ha, that's right
Please help me, Attorney Kang.
Me too
Not this sunless corner
sunny
downtown Seoul
Just looking down~
In an office like this
I want to work
Hahaha
yes, yes
I'll keep an eye on it
Oh, by the way, the pro bono team
When was it made?
Ah, it happened in March of this year.
This March?
Well, it hasn't been that long.
Where did everyone come from?
Uh, Nanhee
While working in a human rights club
I came here right after graduating from law school.
Yeongsil’s brother
That and other public interest organizations
He came from working here and there.
Well, I
Well, well, you probably don't know
That law firm
It's because it's a big hit, and then...
From an unheard of firm
Attorney Park Gi-ppeum
It's an internal support case.
Internal support?
So, are you originally an O&N lawyer?
Yes, I'm from the M&A team.
Wow, that's a team that only sends aces?
That, Park Gi-ppeum
Because I have a strong nerd temperament
It's a little strange sometimes
I'm good at it
Attorney Kang mainly
Park Byun and you will work as a team.
Oh~
I'm happy with that friend
Are you saying we'll be working together?
Originally, Yeongsil’s older brother
I was on a team with Byun Park.
Me and Nanhee will come as a team.
‘Newly established in March of this year’
Founder Oh Gyu-jang
As a successor test, Jeong-in
As soon as he was appointed as the representative lawyer
I mean, we got this team.
Just let your body break down
- Let me give it a try.
- Hmm
- I said this with my own mouth...
- What?
- yes?
- Ugh
- Thanks for the pants.
- Yeah, yeah.
Lawyer, I, he
These days again...
Are you here?
Baby, still
Can't find your room?
Actually
Isn’t our firm a bit big?
Was this it?
Why we created a pro bono team
Did you do some research?
Wow, I was impressed, Oh Jeong-in.
No, the No. 1 law firm in Korea.
I was wondering why they had a team that wasn't making money.
There was a reason for everything, right?
‘A lawyer is’
'More than a certain number of hours per year
Must engage in public interest activities'
So what do you want to say?
Did they sneak in this clause?
'Performed by a public interest lawyer
Time for public interest activities
'The entire law firm
'It is recognized as public interest activity time'
Hey, this, what
The team that goes instead of the reserve forces
You picked it, huh?
My brother is still really crooked.
Just because you don’t do public interest work
It's not like it's a big deal
Everyone is wearing sunglasses
The position of the No. 1 law firm would be different.
It's perfect to get criticized
Well, that's it.
I see you put me there
It seems like he was anxious.
Anyway
O&Partners has a name value.
If the public interest team breaks up again and again
Aiming for four positions
The snakes
I'm going to bite you
Isn't it?
So what do you want to say?
I'm busy
1 year
1 year?
I am those bonobonos
I'll take care of it for just one year.
Their winning rate is
It was only around 20%.
I'll raise it to 50%
This
As a dedicated public interest
The winning rate is close to a miracle, right?
Like an older brother
Do you want to make a deal?
What is the price?
Ah~
the afternoon sunlight
Okay~ coming in
A sunny partner’s office facing southwest?
No, a little further away
Where?
Seocho-dong?
Return to Central District Court?
no, a little more
far away
No way
Supreme Court Justice seat
There will be one more seat available next year.
You know, right?
send me there
That's my condition
Crazy…
With the power of O&Partners
You can do it
Recommended by the Bar Association
Make me a candidate for Supreme Court Justice
The conditions are too strong
Are you saying it's a team that doesn't make money?
I don't have money but
You'll get some applause
O&Partners
never received
applause from the public
Conglomerates, only those in power are defended.
Instead of blame
Helping the weak and fulfilling social responsibilities
The new transformation of O&Partners
A new leader who leads the change
Oh Jeong-in
That's it
Isn’t that your intention in creating that team?
That's how it looks to me
When you've said everything you have to say, go out.
Byung
70%
Damn?
fish oil
70%
The odds of winning are barely 50%
The place value of the Supreme Court Justice of the Republic of Korea
Isn’t that too cheap?
To make a deal
What is the winning rate of ‘Best Baseball’?
Why don't you walk?
Heung
today
You say the accuser will appear in person?
A place where I believe in something
It looks like it's tight. Is it okay?
hmm…
How do I know if I win or lose?
Still
We only do it with sincerity
Ah, boy…
Since David Kang is here
Such a weak sound!
I absolutely cannot tolerate this.
- What are you doing?
-Why my desk...
If you don't understand, memorize it.
We will definitely win
i will make that happen
us now
I don't know why I was called here
For now
-Sue...
- Ji So-yeon~
Where are you?
Me?
- uh!
- What are you doing!
why are you like this
A thief
Where is this shit
Do you covet someone else’s precious dog?
Hey
Hey!
You are our Chloe
Do you know how much it costs?
- This is really...
-Ayu, ayu, madam
Calm down your excitement.
Let go
You guys, the dog cafe is just an excuse.
Stealing a dog
Aren’t you doing business? uh?
What is it?
Are you saying too much?
Please sit down.
What are you again?
These are lawyers.
Assault that just occurred
You can also become a suing attorney.
What are you saying, really?
Are you threatening me now?
Do you know who I am?
Self-exploration of who I am
Do it yourself at home
If you make a reckless complaint without any evidence
Being punished for a false accusation
You know, right?
what?
Can you be a judge?
Why are you talking so high?
You have a sharp eye.
Wait a minute
Rather than stimulating the other person too much now...
my clients
An abandoned dog without a collar
I just adopted it.
If it's such a precious dog
Why didn't I look for it for a year and a half?
Has it just appeared now?
Do you know if I found it or not?
If the real owner appears
You don't have to give it up!
fish oil
Anyway, the prosecution
End with acquittal
By mutual agreement
I will tell you to drop the complaint.
Just a false accusation
Please don't investigate.
Oh, are you here?
Prosecutor, queak
Well said, you.
somewhere in korea
Have a taste of the prosecution.
What?
It’s been a while, Judge Kang.
Woo Myung-hoon
sorry
You're not a judge now, are you? True
Are you a public interest lawyer?
Oh, what happened?
Hey, in an incident like this
A former prosecutor of the Supreme Prosecutors' Office's Central Investigation Department?
An incident like this?
Stealing a dog
Are you a kidnapper of someone else's child?
Same thing
Can't you read the trends of the times?
Uncharacteristically
Are you okay?
Well, what's not to be okay with?
But that accuser
Well, is it okay to be the daughter of a high-ranking prosecutor?
yes
She is the daughter of Rep. Lee Doo-cheol, a former prosecutor.
Ah, somehow...
So what about Woo Myung-hoon?
Do you know each other?
Well, I'm a fellow student at the training center.
Well, we're not in a very affectionate relationship with each other.
As long as Woo Myung-hoon is attached
It won't end easily.
Yes?
uh? Procedures in accordance with the Animal Protection Act
Did you step on it all?
Woo Myung-hoon's specialty
Do you know what it is?
What’s your specialty?
planting evidence
Yes?
- Ouch!
- uh!
- under…
- Draw the picture first
somehow it fits there
I am a human being who creates evidence.
I made my way to success with that.
I got hit with a big one.
Until it goes awry
no
No, then to Attorney Kang.
You even have a grudge, right now?
No, we really
You can win this case, right?
That's good
Hey, what's going well now...
Attorney David Kang
In the first case of opening a business,
I thought it wasn't very impactful
From the Supreme Prosecutors' Central Investigation Department
At least the daughter of a member of the National Assembly should appear.
The picture is pretty
Good
Hey, Attorney Kang.
Why?
no, now
What does it mean to be pretty?
Look ahead, red light
Ugh!
why?
Ha, with an incident like this
Two prosecutors came out.
A former prosecutor general and senior
Because this is the case of the daughter of a powerful member of the Legislative and Judiciary Committee.
But why is the judge late?
If anything happens...
Ah, here is Detective 1 alone.
Judge Oh Jae-seop
Famous for being 5 minutes late
I'll be there in a minute.
Attorney Park
- But why were you so nervous?
- yes?
Maybe
This isn't your first time in court, right?
Ha, I'm not the first.
I have been
Mainly doing corporate advisory work.
criminal court
This is the second time
Boy, still
You've seen a lot of courtroom movies.
You’re a movie fanatic.
Sure
I really like ‘Philadelphia’ too.
‘A Few Good Men’ is the movie of my life.
Okay, it's okay.
Just do it like those movies
confidently
Don’t be scared, be confident
yes
3, 2, 1
all
Please stand up.
Everyone, please take your seats.
This is
Is this a case that would go that far, tsk?
- Attorney Kang
- Yes?
An amicable agreement between both parties
Give the dog back
The complainant withdraws the complaint
Why not?
Why are you making such a fuss?
Your honor!
The defendants have already
With love for over a year and a half
In this case, I raised a dog named Byeol-i...
Chloe!
Unsophisticated…
Be quiet!
Adoption process also
Completed legally
So simply
What you're asking me to do is give Byeol back to you.
before the trial even starts
With words that reveal foresight
lawyer
Hollywood movies
Haven't you seen too much?
- yes?
- This is Korea.
Don't go crazy and do that there.
Go to the defense bar and speak.
Just the basics
yes
sorry
I think it was okay
Child…
Your honor
We recently acquired
There is a strong report
To submit additional evidence
Change the date...
An incident from a year and a half ago...
It's an incident
no, come now
This is a strong report.
Please sit down!
I'm still okay
I can't believe the prosecutors of the Republic of Korea
Are you saying they are manipulating evidence?
Prosecutor, uh, do that.
Now, the next date is…
Your honor?
What is it?
I'm sorry, but
additionally appointed by us
I have a lawyer
I'm a little late right now due to traffic...
Please allow me to attend.
These days, public parties
Are you late for court as well?
sorry
- No.
- Oh my.
Hahaha, oh my, oh my, oh my
Oh my~
This
Sorry for being late, hahaha
Attorney added
It was Attorney Park.
- Ah
- What?
What is this old man that has the judge stumped?
That's it.
Our Honor
- Former court chief here...
- and…
In the case of an abandoned dog
A former member of the Supreme Prosecutor's Central Investigation Department was hired.
This time, is this from the chief judge of the court?
- her…
- Oh, me.
Well, I'm sorry.
Your honor
This, I
Because I was appointed late…
That's right
Uh, added record.
You probably didn't have time to review it.
- Yes
- I'll give you time.
child, thank you
Huh, this is something I only heard about
All-hall power?
Thank you, your honor.
Ugh…
As long as the opponent appears like this
Let's hire a lawyer
Yes? Lawyer Kang transferred to...
Oh, isn't it?
I am the Central District Court.
There are more direct lines.
Leave it to me
In public interest cases
Are you saying they will mobilize all honors?
Why not?
Honorable mention
It's a structural corruption that needs to be eliminated.
How can something like that be done in a public interest case?
The common people
Can't we just take advantage of the courtesy?
Well, people with power and money
They all use the entire building?
still…
Public interest cases
It's a free defense.
In the first place, it was impossible to pay the transfer fee.
There is none
Leave that to me.
Ball!
- Oh, what a surprise.
- Fish oil, slices are so...
Director!
fish oil
Oh my, Judge Kang
Ah, why here again?
Because you don't answer my phone calls
Don't I come this far?
Director
Oh, by the way
Hey, the slice is still the same.
Hey, a little more when I follow through.
Huh? Lightly relax and keep going~
Hey, Judge Kang, why are you really like this?
uh?
In the case of that little dog
What pretense are you using?
That's right
Hey, just like when you were the judge.
It should be at least like the case of the CEO of a large company.
It's correct to use the entire title.
Only then can the judge and all lawyers
I also play golf
I also go to bars
- Go abroad and play golf again.
- Now, wait, wait.
What the hell is this
What are you talking about?
Judge Kang?
Oh no, no, no
It's all in the past, but it's okay.
Hey, it's me
I just have a really good memory.
There are just so many things I picked up.
Oh my, this guy is really…
Director
specially made
This is a slice prevention ball.
- Oh?
- Let's try this.
Yeah?
Let's try it
Nice shot!
You are truly amazing, Attorney Kang.
In a public interest case
Lee, former chief judge of the court
I think this is your first time seeing you?
Is that also free defense?
Now the judge
Would you like to proceed in a less biased manner?
no
The presiding judge ex officio
I will decide to avoid it.
Yes?
Pursuant to Article 24 of the Criminal Procedure Act
Ex officio, this case
Decide to avoid
Your honor?
uh? Your honor!
No, in the same court
Because you have ever worked there?
You have to avoid it to that extent.
Isn't it true?
That's it
It's Judge Oh Jae-seop's style.
Safety first for new breasts
You probably didn't want to be caught in the middle, right?
I don't like being caught in the middle...
Judge Oh
Myung-hoon Woo is a high school junior.
The two of us have a hobby together
Have you ever taken a baking class?
It's been 2 years or something
It's all different.
- Ha!
-Ha
Hey, Mr.
So the judge said out loud
In favor of the prosecution...
from the beginning
Wasn't the purpose to give him honorable mention?
That's pretty cool, Attorney Park.
The goal was to change the court.
But
Do you know?
case to be reassigned
Who is the second criminal judge?
Why, why?
What do you think the next judge will be like?
Is that really stupid?
Selected by the Bar Association for 3 consecutive years
To an unfriendly judge
He is famous for his anger management disorder...
So who the hell are you?
Why, why am I the only one who doesn’t know?
Wow...
Hey, this dog…
mind!
People like you just buy things...
Cover your eyes!
Ugh, yeah
I know
I couldn't get promoted because of my temperament.
With 10 years of juniors
Choi Ho-jip, who I work with
Chief judge.
Oh my god, what should I do?
Of course, the judge spoke harshly…
Are you close with him?
Oh my, can’t that be true?
What Manager Choi hates the most is
a judge like me
Good social skills
a popular judge
Hey
With strength at the last minute...
Now, Manager Kim, snack!
No no
I'm going to eat Bindaetteok
Oh, is it Bindaetteok? Wow
child
How old are you and why are you a picky eater?
Just eat what you get, eat it
This guy!
Ah, well, well…
- I can’t pay for the night…
- Here it is
No, then
Why on earth do you do that to someone like that?
Did you make it a dividend?
Boy, you look nice on the outside, but
Behind a biased judge
To anyone
A judge who treats fairly
Wouldn’t it be more advantageous for us?
ah…
Ah, more than that
Additional evidence presented by the prosecution
Submitted?
Wait a minute
It's 'just a moment' again
Submitted, additional evidence
What is it?
Is this a witness statement report?
Witness?
"Cafe"
Hello, Soyeon.
- Hello
- Oh, you're here!
Welcome, hello
Uh, uh, uh, uh
Don't come, don't come!
Don't come, don't come, don't come!
Oh, you saw it.
You saw it, you saw it, you saw it
star
Come here
That's right, sit down
sit down
- It's being released anywhere.
- Hello
- Hello, teacher.
- That's right, good job.
Ah, yes
I'll prepare something to drink.
Ah, ah, us…
Hey, we're okay, sir, uh
You were so surprised, right?
I'll wash my hands quickly and come back.
- Uh, Soyeon.
- Yes?
Today is
That’s the day, right?
yes
What day is today?
Oh, I…
Soyeon
Would you like to sit down for a moment?
Just me?
uh…
The prosecution
Suddenly, I submitted additional evidence.
Um, yeah, well, some…
When I found Byeol-i
You said you didn't have a necklace, right?
yes
But this time suddenly
A witness showed up
Soyeon
star necklace
I saw him secretly throwing it away...
yes?
ah…
Ugh, that's ridiculous.
What did I throw away somewhere?
He said he saw it dumped in the Han River.
Ha…
Oh, really...
This doesn't make sense, it's a complete lie.
-Who said that?
- Right?
When your lawyer was the prosecutor
He was good at manipulating evidence.
Oh, just in case, I guess…
What happened?
ah…
No, sir.
Oh, it's nothing to worry too much about.
no
I think it's something to worry about.
What does that mean all of a sudden?
Not the Han River
Where did you throw it away?
Ha, really…
Oh, what now?
What are you talking about?
Not the Han River
Where did you throw it away?
Where I left the necklace
Ah, lawyer.
How do you see me, I…
I'm not that bad of a person.
Is Soyeon a good person?
Is he a bad person?
Uh, I'm not interested in that.
Just answer the questions asked
Where did you throw away your necklace?
Where did you say you found the dog?
Seongbukcheon
Is that right?
- Did you throw it away there?
- No, Attorney Kang.
Based on what
Are you saying it so definitively?
No, right? Soyeon
you can't do that
No, right?
Ha, really…
Ah, boss
Oh, that's not it...
Perjury or false statements
It's only detrimental to the boss.
What should I do?
Oh, what should I do?
Oh, sorry.
Huh…
- Wow
- Did you really abandon it?
Oh, uh…
Then the eyewitness statement
It wasn't manipulated...
No, it's true that it was fabricated.
Woo Myung-hoon secured during his time as a prosecutor.
I recruited a decent ex-convict.
I must have made a statement, whatever.
Just do it one more time
Prosecutor
Please let me go, son of a bitch.
Ouch!
iced coffee…
Go to the prosecutor's office and make a statement
Memorize the scenario
Don't make the date wrong like last time.
Look closely at the picture of the dog.
Then there were no witnesses.
Soyeon
Is it true that you threw away the necklace?
I'm so upset
no
How on earth do you know this?
first reaction
First, first reaction?
About things you want to hide
When asked a question suddenly
conditionally and reflexively
A defensive reaction comes out first.
- ‘Where is it?’
- That doesn't make sense.
What did I throw away somewhere?
If nothing like that happens
Without any unnecessary sacrifices
He probably denied it right away.
'I'm not a bad person'
‘How do you view me’, blah blah blah
like this
It's a needless thing to do
That's it
It is an instinctive human defense response.
yes, that's right
I asked where did you throw it away?
Because it's the Han River, it's instantaneous
Soyeon’s expression brightened slightly.
He said he saw it dumped in the Han River.
Ha…
Oh, really...
This doesn't make sense, it's a complete lie.
Who said that?
Lawyer Kang
- Yes
- You're really amazing, really.
really
Just wear a legal uniform
If you sit on the judge's bench for a long time,
I can see everything
Big~
Now answer
Why did you lie like that?
necklace
Because of the necklace.
Yes?
A necklace?
hello
Why are you here alone?
huh?
The puppy
You must have been surprised, but you didn’t bark~
Huh?
don't worry
I'll make sure to find your house
What is this?
oh?
Anti-bark collar?
Yes, every time the dog barks
It's a necklace that gives electric shock.
under…
Oh, that's ridiculous.
No, something like that
Are you using it on your dog?
In our country
Isn't it illegal?
Oh, that doesn't mean I'm talking about someone else's dog
What if I bring you like that?
pet supplies voltage
How strong is it when you count it?
Why?
Would you like to try it yourself?
What?
In our organization
I got some as a sample.
Wait a minute
Why do you need to do that...
Hey, what is it?
Oh well, it looks like a kids toy
Well, are you asking me to try this?
yes
Try it yourself
Oh, well
There's nothing you can't do, right?
Is it okay to kick it like this?
Ah, well, it's a bit stuffy.
yes, how, what
Can I at least bark?
- month!
- Wow
month!
- uh? uh?
- uh?
- month! Ouch!
- uh! uh! uh!
Uh, Attorney Kang! Uh, wait a minute
Just a moment, just a moment, just a moment, just a moment
fish oil
Uh, here…
This, something like this
Stuffing it down your dog’s neck?
So
Is that why you didn't bark?
Oh my, it's a star
Ah…
honey
What Byul was wearing
The voltage is stronger
It was a product whose import was banned.
Plus there
Setting a maximum voltage limit
They even released it on purpose.
Ah…
- Wow
- These bad people!
You discovered circumstances of abuse.
Then why didn't you report it right away?
Report?
What good does that do?
What's the use?
I have to report it
Investigated for animal cruelty
I understand why you didn't report it.
Even if I reported it
In the end, to the owner who abused me
Because I have to send it back
Legally this is
Because it's still the owner's property.
So that's it?
yes
Me, that star
Never ever deal with people like that again
I didn't want to send it back
So I stopped…
Sorry, boss.
Why, when you were having such a hard time, I
I really did ask for that.
It's all my fault
Of course it's Soyeon's fault.
Uh, let's talk about it in detail.
That's just the motive for the crime.
Soyeon has an owner
I brought you here knowingly.
That's a crime
I see.
That's how it happened
today
Would you like to leave later?
our star
Because it's a day to eat a full meal.
The stars feed me
Let’s all share together.
What…
What are you sharing?
Come on, let's sit down.
Our Hanbyul
happy birthday
No, never!
No, are you really okay?
Oh, I'm going with my friends, whatever.
Oh, don't worry, don't worry
I told you it wouldn’t work!
They say so many people gather together
If you happen to get hurt somewhere,
What are you trying to do?
Ah~
grandmother
Grandma tell me something, okay?
Oh, I love that street festival
I really wanted to go there.
Oh, something special is happening.
I heard a lot of people are going with their friends.
Are you not worried?
Don’t you even think about this guy’s mother and father?
Oh, let's talk about that now
Why are you doing this?
grandmother
I'm sorry
Even those
In that complicated summer vacation season
I'm going to leave my child and go out to play.
That happened while driving in the rain.
Even if you think I’m foolish
I can't do it
Ah~
Grandpa, I’ll be really careful.
Grandfather, yes?
- promise
- Oh, you too
Wow, what could be going on?
I want to go there too
Should I try wearing my school uniform too?
That's so nice, Grandma!
I'll lend you mine
Wow
Our pretty star
You look so pretty today
Shall we take a picture?
Yeah, okay
Now, one, two, three
Hanbyeol-ah
my pretty baby
Star
Ah, boss
Within a week
What if I can’t find a new owner?
Oh, they say we have to euthanize him.
But my room
Pets are not allowed?
so
How could it not?
I will never again
I don't want to create any relationship
This cafe will be closed soon too.
Honestly, I have no desire to live any longer.
So
- Stop taking him back.
- Uh, boss.
one night
Then just for one night
Can you let him sleep here?
I have a part-time job at night.
I will definitely take you tomorrow
Yes?
grandmother
Hanbyeol-ah
Hanbyeol, ayu, my pretty baby
Ah, my dog
Grandma, don't cry
I'm in a really good place right now
Live happily every day
So, grandma
Don't cry
Huh?
never
Don't think such bad thoughts
You have to live for a long time before coming
Okay?
Hanbyeol-ah
I say a prayer of thanks every day
I didn't go with my grandmother that day.
You don't know how lucky I am
What could I do?
That's a relief, right?
It's a star
Oh, it's a star
Ah…
Is there really no way?
They are punished
Byeol-i says to the people who did such things
go back again
No, what kind of law is this?
Legal provisions are always beautiful, but
Reality is a gutter
I'm sure everyone knows it well.
Let's go
I don't know
In this gutter-like reality
how to win
I don't know yet
I don't know, so you can teach me.
Maybe you can give me a chance
I…
Me too, I will do anything
Uh, I
As much joy as
I don't have good legal skills
Well, as much as Yeongsil hyung.
I'm not very talented
Still, if you run with your feet
I'm really confident
What are the expressions?
I can't believe this Kang David
In the first case of practicing lawyer
Did you think you were going to lose?
Right?
Is there some way?
Lawyer Kang
Uh, Attorney Kang.
I came to Seongbukcheon after a long time.
Let's go to the field
I will live
Uh, okay, yes!
By the way, Park Byun
That was me earlier
in some drama
I think you heard that?
- What?
- 'Because I don't know'
‘You can teach me.’
‘I could give you a chance.’
I have this
Where do you think I heard that?
Well, it's probably because of my mood.
yes
Let's go quickly, yes.
- How do I feel?
- Let's go
- Quickly!
- You also heard yellow stool, right?
yes? What do you mean by that?
Me, the lawyer
- Yes, your honor.
- You submitted it in writing, right?
Well then, what
‘It is true that I threw away the necklace’
Well, then you're pleading guilty.
No, your honor.
Ah, then, well…
Hey, then what should we do?
What should I do…
Ha, is there more to do?
Your honor
This case trial
Please finish it early...
We are
Apply for citizen participation trial
Oh, what?
We claim innocence
Our defendants
to receive a fair trial
I hope for a public participation trial.
‘Fair trial’?
Ah, well, my trial is
'It's not fair.
Well, I have that suspicion.'
You mean that?
Your honor
Because of this incident
Applying to the National Council of Ministers
This is a typical trial delay tactic.
Don't get caught up in these tricks...
Oh, it's noisy!
yes?
The trial progress
I decide for myself.
Do this or that! Mr.
Hey, your honor.
We also have the right to express our opinions...
Ah, then let me be a judge, judge!
judge
child, child, child
Yeah, well, well, yeah, ah...
Well, okay, kid, whatever.
If that's the original, then what?
Yeah, whatever.
Public participation trial?
uh? And what, a fair trial?
Oh, that, what
Let's do it! uh
Let's go somewhere, okay?
seed…
Thank you, your honor.
What trick did that person do again...
ruler! now
Let's prepare our weapons
Attorney Park
Prepare your legal argument.
- Yes
- Attorney Jang?
Uh, keep doing what you're doing.
- Yellow stool?
- Please leave everything to me.
Shall I research precedents?
Running with both feet
You said you were confident, right?
Now
- Attorney Yoo
- Yes
I'm not in charge of this case
You said you would help with anything, right?
yes
Always ‘young looking’, ‘like a baby’
Well, don’t you hear this often?
Wait a minute
Comments about a coworker's appearance
Sexual harassment...
Do you want to try Undercover?
her! Undercover?
Hey, not that fanatic.
This is the sub-workplace.
Team leader? Anger control disorder!
it's about disability
Promoting prejudice!
Hello, mother?
Oh, yeah~
- Are you Somini?
- Yes
- Welcome.
- Hehe
No, you
They say he teaches recorder so well.
Our Areum’s performance evaluation is
I'm worried because there's only a week left.
mother
You have to trust me completely.
Breathing technique is important for the recorder.
From my breathing method
I will teach you a new lesson
Ho~
Uh, yeah, uh, I'll believe it
But
Are you really a high school student?
Hmm, why?
Don't you look like that high school student?
Hmm, that's straight
Hmm, sullen
Yeah yeah
Oh, but I'm a bit older...
They say it's presbyopia
That's right, hahahaha!
Oh, what am I really doing?
under…
-Where are you?
- Mom
What is that guy doing?
Let's see somewhere else.
Don't make eye contact for no reason
Ha…
Ouch! It's my waist
Ah…
Anyway, this
Aren't you running around too much?
Lawyer Kang
yes
2015 Pyeongtaek Station
Pomeranian abuse case
Is there a precedent…
I pulled it out
yes, thank you
Argh!
what?
Me~ long
Huh...
auntie!
Oh, how much does this cost?
- I know, this!
- melong, melong
This is expensive, this, this
How are you going to ask?
No, a snake, a snake came out...
under…
This is just a kid's toy snake!
ah…
Ah, yes, yes, ah, ma’am.
Oh, sorry, oops.
Not once or twice, really
Aunt
Just work until this week
Yes? Madam!
What was broken
I will deduct it from your salary.
I know so
Areum was surprised~
No, madam!
Ah, so suddenly
What if you tell me to leave?
Ah, madam!
Then today's meeting is
Should we stop here?
Well, today I
I'm on my way to a meeting at the Ministry of Justice.
Well, everyone talks a lot, right?
'To O&Partners
'What happened?'
‘Well, even this abandoned dog incident.
‘Are you doing it?’, indeed.
Because of this
I didn't bother to deal with the prosecution.
Our firm’s sales
Do you think it will help?
Take your hands off me right now
Oh, by the way
Speaking of sales,
These are the sales figures for the last 6 months for the two of you.
Ugh, I'm so scared of time passing.
Right?
In the past, the two of you
You took responsibility for our firm’s sales.
Ah, if you look below,
Secretary and driver salary for two people
This is the amount and details of corporate card usage.
Please refer to it
oh lawyer
Yes, Attorney Cha.
If you don't have anything to say, leave it alone.
- What happened?
- what?
They say you can’t do it?
Abandoned dog incident
The #1 law firm is like this
They make a lot of noise and can't get out of their way
Out of shape
Isn't that what you're after?
I'm just doing my best?
Don't need the best, just get the results
You can't lose your granddaughter twice.
Jeong In-ah
I also went to that street festival
that day
Make sure to win, that incident
coming in
After…
Dear Judge,
And the jury
Based on the testimony just
I will make an argument for the defense.
emergency evacuation
or because it constitutes a legitimate act.
gentlemen of the jury
If you are
What would you like to do?
The lady
You're saving a life.
kid, what
Why do I do that...
I've never been there before
Hey, I've noticed...
Ugh~
Huh?
Ouch!
lawyer
Examine the witnesses
yes
witness
The witness was at the complainant's house.
You've been working as a housekeeper for three years, right?
yes
The abandoned dog in this case was also
You know, right?
yes
That kid
I made a fuss about wanting a big dog.
This is the dog my wife bought.
But the kid is so moody
I got tired of it quickly.
Oh, I see.
After that, about the abandoned dog in this case
Would the treatment be different?
Hey, what are you doing?
It has become a very sad place.
‘It costs a lot of money.
‘Give only half of the food each.’
‘The sound of dogs barking is annoying’
Aunt
Oh, then
Where and what kind of dog collar do you get
I saved you
After that, he stopped barking.
Maybe
Was it a necklace like this?
I wore it like this
Now once
Let me try to make a sound
Month, month, month!
This is right at the beginning
It's not a shock
beep once
It rings like this
I once again
Let's try it
Month!
Ugh
Your honor
This question has nothing to do with this case.
It matters
How warm is that...
Abuse site
On the premise of our argument
This is a relevant question
Your honor
yes
Do it, keep going
witness
I just saw that
Is this the right type of necklace?
yes, that's right
Every time the dog barks, I bark
He said he wanted to die from pain.
Ah, it's a little thing, but
How pitiful
This is a court
You can't wear sunglasses
Shhh!
Undercover
But why has a year and a half passed?
Are you suddenly looking for a dog?
Kids are fickle, right?
Ah, with my friends
I went to a dog cafe
I guess I saw that dog.
‘Why is my dog at someone else’s house?’
‘Bring it to me right away’
Just crying and crying
Because of the uproar...
I have an objection!
The theft has already been committed
What happened after that has nothing to do with the incident.
- I admit it…
- Yes, I admit it.
I withdraw the question
The questions and answers I just heard are
Please pretend it never happened.
Defender, defender!
yes
That means
That judgment is
I, the judge, am speaking.
Do you know?
Oh, sorry.
Stop following the habits that were ingrained in you from your previous job...
- Wow
- Okay, go in, go in.
I will be careful
Dear Judge,
And the jury
As you just saw, the abandoned dog in this case was
electric shock
I've been suffering all day
was in a state of severe starvation
Defendant Ji So-yeon
In this case, the abandoned dog
If you send it back to the abuser
Something more terrible
I thought it would happen
Break the necklace
It found a new owner
This is
emergency evacuation or
Because it is a legitimate act
I'm not guilty
This is a ridiculous claim.
How far can emergency evacuation go?
An imminent danger to people
It is established when it occurs
For dogs that are merely property of their owners
Emergency evacuation?
This guy doesn't even know the basics of criminal law
It's just a claim
yes, that's right
Animals are just objects under the law.
Then you don't even know the basics of criminal law.
I will ask the prosecutor.
If animals are just objects
A person who abuses his or her property
Why are you accused of animal cruelty?
Are you punishing me?
- that…
- Let me ask you again.
Prosecutor's colleague
Seniors at the Ministry of Justice
You studied hard and made it.
Civil Code Amendment Act, Article 98-2, Paragraph 1
Did you know?
'animals'
'It's not a thing'
Animals are not objects
It's life, prosecutor.
Defendant Ji So-yeon
Just one life
I wanted to protect it
Dear common sense citizens of this country,
If you are
What would you like to do?
To the owner who repeats abusive behavior
I have no choice but to send it back
new owner
If you don't find it within a certain period of time
This is a situation that requires euthanization.
This act of defendant Ji So-yeon
really
Do you think it's a crime?
That's it.
Yes, good job
Oh, it's pretty good?
It's a bit of a 'lawyer' tone, though.
It might have worked
Your honor
If it weren't for that kid...
As the plaintiff's representative
I also want to say something
Okay, then, over there.
I come out here
Uh, come out and make sure we're heard.
Thank you, your honor.
Now the defense
According to a well-prepared script
maliciously against the complainant
I'm framing you.
Witness just one thing
What to ask
May I make a request?
Please speak
The witness is the accuser
Have you ever stolen a pearl necklace?
please ask
I have an objection!
This question is not related to this case.
no
This is a related question
defense witness
It's a question about the credibility of the statement.
Witness, did you hear?
Please answer
Yes?
No
Oh, I'm not that kind of person.
Uh, why did I
Do you touch other people's things?
The complainant
Always keep your valuables in the room where you keep them.
We have installed a camera.
Video recording of the crime scene
Submit as evidence
no
I, I…
No, that's not it.
Oh, I
In this house, with this excuse and that excuse
The salary I didn't receive
It's over 10 million won.
He suddenly told me to stop...
I just
Uh, at least the money I get
I thought I should get it and leave...
so?
You guys so far
Stealing belongings from the owner's house
You heard the thief's testimony.
dog abuse
It's a ridiculous slander.
The complainant
A pet dog that I cherished like my own child.
Stolen by unscrupulous people
In great mental pain
I've been suffering
I have an objection
Don't insult the defendants
Also, the defense attorney
Other than the prepared false testimony
There is no physical evidence
Unable to present
electric torture collar
If there is such a thing
Please present it as evidence.
Isn't it? pleader?
Oh, and Attorney Park.
That touching speech from earlier
I heard you well
But what you said
‘Animals are not objects’ amendment
Was it passed by the National Assembly?
Is it done?
Not yet
Are you there yet?
Ah, you said it so confidently.
I thought it had already passed
To you non-expert jurors,
Even more so
I think you misunderstood?
Maybe
If that's what you were aiming for
I was even more impressed
very promising
You're a lawyer.
How far can I go
Social norms are changing
In terms of purpose...
That's it for now, your honor.
Good job, please come in.
No more, whatever.
If you don't have any questions
Uh, that's the end of the witness questioning.
Uh, just a moment before closing arguments.
I'll take a break
under…
Ha, sorry
I should have looked into it more closely.
No, it’s okay, Nanhee.
No, how can something like that happen?
You could have known it all
Oh no
Ah, but what should I do?
I should have that necklace at least
I will prove the fact of abuse.
It's time to come...
yes?
- Attorney Kang!
- You're here.
Hwang Jun-woo?
haha…
What about things?
sorry
I thought I finally found it
No, it was just
When it rained last time
It was just some miscellaneous floating down.
Ah…
Was it too much?
sorry
Oh, what should I do?
Attorney Kang?
Is this now a dead end?
I need to go to the bathroom for a moment
I feel so clean in this situation
Why is it like that?
pleader?
Hey, lawyer!
Animals are objects
prosecution's argument
This is all legally correct.
Under current law, companion animals are
an object owned by the owner
That's right
to get things
emergency evacuation, legal action
There is no way the court would admit it.
I know very well
A society that doesn’t even take care of people properly.
You even care about the lives of animals?
It sounds like you are full.
Attorney Kang, are you crazy?
Your honor, I just
Just one thing for the accuser
I'd like to check
Examination of witnesses against the complainant
please allow
Hey, then
lawyer
very briefly
Let's keep it simple
yes
Me, the accuser!
Please come to the witness stand.
Yes?
Come out!
yes
Your honor
Show it to the accuser
There is an object
Enlargement No. 12
Bringing it into court
please allow
Attorney, Exhibit No. 12: That is...
Oh, that's...
yes
It's just evidence
Is it a thing?
Even in court
Can't it be submitted?
How should I do this?
Should I get it?
Shouldn't it be done?
Ha, really...
Oh, oh, yeah, whatever
yes
thank you
Practitioner
Hey, oh my
Huh…
It's a star!
Ah, uh
uh
Ah, star
Uh, yeah
Ah…
What is a pet?
This is what it is
I don't want to hear my owner barking.
Put a stun gun on my neck
Even if my throat burns
Because the owner is too lazy to throw it away
Hoping to starve to death
Even if you don't feed me
Even if I meet such an owner after a long time
Without realizing it
A being that licks the back of its owner's hand
Only
To love only people
created being
That's a pet
Ha…
Okay, look at the juror's face.
Ah, I have mental symptoms, but I don’t have physical evidence.
How are you going to prove the abuse?
who are these
Did you make it like this?
It's us humans
wild life
Let’s grab it greedily
By taming and breeding
us humans
I have no choice but to love instinctively
I made it into existence
Yes, we made it according to our needs.
When there is no need for it
I guess I can just throw it away.
for things like that
Emergency evacuation, legitimate action claim
I will withdraw
Your honor
I just lastly
the most basic facts
Just recheck one thing
Let me conclude my argument.
Yeah, well, yeah
witness
Please take a closer look at this dog.
Please take a closer look.
Stay still
Ha, ha…
necklace
Did you really think I threw it away?
under…
Witness, one simple question
You can answer
This dog now
a dog owned by a witness
Is that correct?
yes?
uh?
what are you doing?
Now come
Again, what does that mean?
criminal trial
beyond reasonable doubt
It has to be proven
If there is only a 1% chance of error
until the end of the trial
till the end
one more time
You have to be suspicious
Actually, if you think about it
Dogs of the same breed and similar size
Isn't that a lot?
witness
Take a good look
A real witness
lost
Is it a dog?
I think you're a little confused.
Let’s take a sip of water.
-Why is it like that?
- Why are you doing that?
under…
Hey there
Your honor
Oh, yes, say it.
I'm so unwell
That's right
Just 5 minutes...
Can I just take a 5 minute break?
Well, if you really say so
We will take a 10 minute break.
What's going on?
Lawyer
What are you doing now?
What is it?
It's a dog owned by a witness.
It's a star
Are you okay?
yes, it's okay
David Kang, that human is in trouble
Are you out of your mind?
But don't get caught up
Let's finish it quickly
yes
Oh my, it's 10 minutes.
Now, what, how?
Are you feeling better, witness?
Yes~
Hahaha, I'm glad
Ah, I just don't understand.
I'm checking.
No, isn't it?
Former prosecutor
The daughter of a three-term congressman
Growing up in a family that was a guardian of law and order
An educated witness
illegally imported
electric shock collar
Fill it with your dog
Starving and leaving you until you die
Did he do such terrible things?
Wow~
If by any chance that's true
If even conclusive evidence comes out
This, this, this, this!
very, very
I'm going to go crazy?
In the news, in newspapers, on social media
Hey, can't that be true?
Your Honor, the defense attorney is
Claims of unproven facts
Continuing...
hey! Please sit down
witness
What now?
It's your last chance
Once again in great detail
Please take a closer look
Cruelly abused and abandoned
This poor abandoned dog
really lost witness
Is that the dog?
Ah, the fact of abuse
Unless it can be proven
The complainant said it was not his dog.
I have no choice but to make him change his words.
Is that possible?
There's no evidence?
no
Yeah, what?
I can't hear very well
Could you speak a little louder?
No
No, no
That dog
She looks a lot like our Chloe
If you look closely, it's not true.
Our Chloe
It was different from those hybrids.
Me!
I'll cancel the complaint.
sorry
I
I was mistaken!
That dog!
My dog!
no!
Wait a minute
Witness, what are you doing? yes?
Ah, come now
What do you mean?
yes?
yes
You can bark as much as you want now
Ah, our star
you are not chloe
Hey, lawyer.
Hey, are you finished with the paper?
Yes, that's it
Now, if the newspaper is over
Please take me out.
Oh, star!
ah…
Boy, you seem confused.
Let’s take a sip of water.
right now
call your dad
Dad?
Hey, man
Are you crazy?
Dad, what's wrong?
Judge Kang, that person
He just called me threatening.
what are you
Are you saying there was animal abuse or something?
I heard there is all the physical evidence.
Is that true?
No, Dad, that's not it...
If by any chance that's true
My nomination for this general election is
It's flying
in my constituency
Do you know how many hundreds of thousands of companion animals there are?
Because of you
On the day my political life ends
I don't think you'll ever open your hands to me again
don't even dream
Areum is studying abroad and nothing else!
- Do you understand?
- Dad
Dad!
That ah…
dad!
dad…
ah! Mr.
no
This…
What happened to this?
What is that star necklace?
I obviously couldn't find it?
well?
I don't know either?
I can't find it in the market
Talented Attorney Jang
Any good ideas?
hmm…
It's the leather part.
At Cheonggyecheon
It's easy to do with fabric.
The metal buckle part is
Bring something similar
If you do some welding
I think it will come out somewhat similar.
Please give me two days
It'll be enough to fool your eyes for a moment.
Well anyway
We win now, right?
in the faces of the jurors
The conclusion has already been drawn, right?
and…
Even though I know, they deceive me
No, anyway, the accuser
He said it wasn't his dog, so what?
- Yeah.
- Uh
No, but I don't know yet
These jurors
Even if you try to find a not guilty verdict
The judge said it was a clear error
You can turn it over
It can be so
But
Judge Choi Ho-jip won't do that.
Why? That judge
They say I'm a very stubborn old brat.
What's your name~?
name, name
hand
- hand
- Judge Choi's nickname is Dog Father.
Maybe it's because you don't have kids.
Three abandoned dogs
You adopted me and raised me.
Oh my, yeah
-What is this dog leash? Pretty things too...
- Wow, the world is like that.
They say you can’t be kind?
Hmm
Heh!
Then
1 It’s not just about avoiding the single thing.
From the very beginning, to Judge Choi Ho-jip.
Are you planning on getting it distributed?
under… So cool
Ha! Unlucky
- Ha…
- I can hear everything!
Okay then
I'll make a ruling, there.
Defendants, please stand up.
of the jury
Respecting consensus of opinion
To the defendants
I find you not guilty.
Ah…
- Of course not guilty.
- Wow
Thank goodness, really.
Please stand up.
Plaintiff!
Chloe, that's your dog!
Look at something wrong!
- You're being generous.
- What's wrong, really...
thank you
Wow, thank you
Really Lawyer Kang
Really, really...
It's been a while
CEO Jaebeom Yoo
Yes, it's been a while.
CEO Oh
Ah, that
Thank you very much
Attorney Kang
Why did you come to Pro Bono?
Who are you suing?
God
I want to receive compensation for my damages
I said no
I'm in this world
Being alive itself is a loss.
Even if you don't win...
What is a trial
Is this a public broadcast to help needy neighbors?
I'm making money
It's the best public interest.
Let’s listen, let’s listen, really!
What a brat!
If the defendant is God
Where should I send the delivery address?
I'm not sure
Dogok-ro 101
I go there
I will send you a complaint for damages.
Hey, do you live in Gangnam?
It may be a ridiculous idea, but
If this all has some intention...
He must be a runaway teenager.
Like Jeong So-min
Woongsan Group Choi Woongsan
- sue the chairman
- This is crazy...
I'll take you to court.
Ah!
- 아유
- 아, 엄마
나 아파 죽겠어
아유, 그래도
- 이만하길 천만다행이지
- 아, 아, 아
큰일 날 뻔했어, 다윗아
진짜 내가 그놈의 개 새끼, 씨
다시 만나기만 해 봐
아주 그냥
다리 몽둥이를 분질러서, 씨
- 아…
- That won't happen.
-Why?
- Once you bite someone
They say it becomes a habit
The man of the house
Right now tonight
They said they were selling that dog.
Really?
What should I do? The owner said so.
Well, let's see, fish oil!
David!
Oh, it's this dog
No!
uh?
- Oh, David!
- No, mister!
Hey, get out of the way!
- No, man.
- I'm hurt!
No, man.
Don't let the general send you!
Hey, once a dog bites a person
I can't raise it because it's a habit.
Uh, uh, get out of the way!
I keep touching it
It's because I was joking.
Oh, so don't let the general send you!
Oh, I really...